chrisnguyen@zenonzeni.ca

### **Summary**

Currently a 4<sup>th</sup> year honors student in information technology at York University & Tutoring at Code Ninjas on hw to program and make software applications. My goal is to become an IT developer that has worked on projects using Java an object-oriented programming language, PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS (Bootstrap), JavaScript (JSON, JQUERY, AJAX), SQL (MySQL, Oracle) for testing, implementing, and designed web pages, websites, and applications. I have personal experience in system administration and designing/testing web IT systems.

### WORK EXPERIENCE & RELATED EXPERIENCE

## **Coding Instructor & Curriculum Developer** June 2021 – Present

| 1 Year | Code Ninjas, Vogel Richmond Hill, Ontario

- In-person and virtually develop video games and teach ninjas how to make games, videos, robots.
- Teach how to make JavaScript games, Roblox games and Unity (C#) games.

### Academic Peer Support Assistant | May 2020 – April

2022 | 2 Years | York University, Vaughan, Ontario

- Facilitate study session for students by analyzing, design, develop and test java programs.
- Students who took part of my study sessions do a whole grade letter better in the course.

# Ride Operator | March 2018 - November 2019

2 Years | Canada Wonderland, Vaughan,

#### Ontario

- Participated in teams of more than ten and communicate with other associates to operate rides.
- We would follow best practices to meet ride performance goals and safety audits.

# Web Developer | Volunteer | Indigenous Friends | Oct 2021 – Present

• Designing, developing, and deploying an AI Virtual Chat Bot using IBM Watson Assistant.

### **Personal and Academic Projects**

#### **Portfolio Website Project**

Developed a website portfolio at <a href="https://zenonzeni.ca">https://zenonzeni.ca</a>.

# Web Camping Spot Reservation System (Prototype)

Developed a web-based information system at http://132.145.111.100/.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Honors Bachelor Information Technology** | 2018–2022 | GPA: B+|

York University, Vaughan, Ontario

### Skills, Knowledge & Tools

## **Programming Languages and Frameworks**

• HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQUERY, AJAX, JSON, PHP, and Java

# **Database Languages**

• SQL (MYSQL, SQLPlus, Oracle)

## System Administration/DevOps Skills

• Linux/Unix, MySQL, Oracle DB, IBM cloud tools, AWS, Oracle, Apache, Tomcat, Key Encryption, SSH, FTP, GIT.

### Tools/Knowledge

• Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook, Word, Zoom, (NetBeans, Eclipse Visual Studios, IntelliJ), etc.